tradestead.com 2011-05-23

# Privacy Policy Information - Wholesale Electronics - China Dropship

Tradestead.com and its subsidies (collectively referred to in this Privacy Statement as "we" or "Tradestead") recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of all information provided by users of our web sites and customers of our products and services. We created this policy with a fundamental respect for our customers' right to privacy and to guide our relationships with our customers. This Privacy Statement discloses the privacy practices for all products and services owned by Tradestead. 

**Information Collection and Use**  
Tradestead is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any outside parties, except as outlined in this policy. We collect information from our customers to process orders and better serve you with pertinent information, such as order confirmations and order status updates. Information collected includes your name, shipping address, billing address, telephone numbers, e-mail address, and payment information such as your credit card number. We also require you to submit a username and password of your choice for your future access to your account information. To safeguard that your username and password remain confidential, DO NOT share this information with anyone. If you elect to receive our newsletters or special promotions, your contact information will be used for the delivery of these items. 

**Registration**  
In order to process your orders placed on this website, you must first complete the registration form. During registration, you will be required to provide your contact information, which includes your name, e-mail address, telephone number and street address. This information is used to provide you with important Tradestead services such as automated order status updates via e-mail. 

**Order**  
Most of the information collected in the registration process will be used to process orders. During the order process, you will have to provide financial information such as your credit card number, expiration date, money order, wire transfer or check information. This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this contact information to get in touch with you. To properly process your credit card information, we must share your personal and financial information with the merchant bank for authorization and approval. This process is protected by an enhanced security system. See the Security section below for more details on security measures and procedures. We do not share your personal and financial information with any third parties, except those specified in the Sharing section of this policy. 

**Cookies**  
We customize certain Web page content based upon your browser type and other information provided by our cookie. If you choose to reject the cookie, you can still browse our store but will be unable to use the shopping cart to buy merchandise. The Tradestead shopping cart cannot function without cookies enabled so that the necessary information to process your order is retained. If you disable cookies, Tradestead will be unable to accept your online order. We will not share any personally identifiable information provided by this cookie with any third party. We will, however, link data stored in cookies to the personally identifiable information you submitted while on our site. This allows us to personalize your shopping experience and discern user preferences to evoke subconscious feelings of familiarity and assurance. 

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information except for security purposes, and we do not distribute or share IP information with any third parties. 

**Sharing**  
We may employ third party companies to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include order fulfillment, package delivery, marketing assistance, postal and e-mail delivery, customer service, data analysis, and credit processing. The third parties we contract for these purposes have limited access to your personal information and may not use it for other purposes.   
As our business continues to evolve, we may acquire or sell business units or subsidiaries. Customer information is one of the business assets that would be transferred in these types of transactions. In such a situation, your personally identifiable information would only be used in a manner consistent with our pre-existing Privacy Notice.We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**Children and Minors**  
Tradesterad does not sell products for purchase by children and minors. Youth-oriented products are sold for purchase by adults only. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use Tradestead in the presence of a consenting parent or guardian. We will not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information via the Internet from children under the age of 16. Tradestead is committed to protecting the welfare and privacy of children and minors. 

**Links**  
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Tradestead is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website. 

**Security**  
Tradestead takes precautions to protect its customers' information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.When our registration/order form asks you to enter sensitive information (such as your credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software currently available in the industry \- SSL. Tradestead uses the most advanced form of SSL software available: 128-bit encryption. To learn more about SSL, follow this link [www.verisign.com ](http://www.verisign.com/).Access to all of our users' information is restricted. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. For added security, only partial information of your billing information is stored in our secured and encrypted database. You may also contact us to request that your information be deleted from our database. For future transactions, you will be required to re-enter your information.All Tradestead servers, including web servers and database servers, are housed and maintained in secure locations. Access to the database is strictly monitored and protected from outside access. Internet access is restricted and protected by multiple checkpoints, firewalls and password protection. The servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secured environment, inside a secured and locked room. All backups are stored and locked in a high-level security room. Only personnel with proper security clearance have access to these restricted areas. Tape backups are not permitted to leave the premises without prior authorization.All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. In addition to any time a new policy is added, Tradestead employees are periodically notified and/or reminded about the importance of new privacy and what they can do to ensure that customers' information remains protected at all times.If you have any questions or concerns about Tradestead's security practices, you can send us an email at [services@tradestead.com ](mailto:service@tradestead.com).  
 **

Special Offers

**  
Our special offers are sent only to customers who grant Tradestead permission to send them such information.To honor the privacy of our users, we offer the option to not receive these types of communications. At the time of your order, you may opt to not receive special offers and news by clicking the appropriate field. Furthermore, all special offers are sent via e-mail and include an opt-out link if you no longer wish to receive special offers and news. Customers might still receive intermittent updates on products, services, specials or Tradestead news. Please refer to the Choice/Opt-out section below for further details on how to be removed from our mailing list should you choose to be removed.  
 **

Correction/Updating/Reviewing Personal Information

**  
Customers may change or review their stored account information such as street address or e-mail address through our website. You must have your username and password in order to access your account. In the event you forget both your username and password, please contact our customer service department for assistance. 

**Choice/Opt-out**  
For customers who wish to opt-out and stop receiving Tradestead special offers and related news, Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletters or promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these communications by updating their stored account information through our website, or send e-mails to [services@tradestead.com ](mailto:services@tradestead.com)with a request to be removed. 

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.If you have opted out of receiving communications from Tradestead, you will still be able to view news of policy changes at [www.tradestead.com ](http://www.tradestead.com/). Otherwise, you may contact us for changes and updates.

_Last Updated: June 1, 2005_
